I'm Aaron Summers here with the Saints
newest punter, Ryan Wright. Welcome to
the Saints. You returned to New Orleans
after having played here with Tulain.
What are you looking forward to most
about being back in the city?
>> Um, I'm excited to be back with some
really great friends that I made in
college. Um, there's a lot of people in
this building, too, that I know as well.
Um, I'm excited to experience the
culture again. The food is great here.
Um, yeah, just really happy to be back.
you were able to actually play in the
dome practice with Tulain and here in
the indoor facility. What are you
looking forward to about being able to
actually take the field and play in the
Super Dome in a game?
>> Oh, yeah. It's a dream. Uh never in my
imagination I would be in this position
where I'd actually be playing for the
team that I I I practice in the dome and
and this practice facility behind us
like you said. Um but we're here and I'm
I'm excited to get to work.
>> What did you like about being able to
come here and join the Saints? Um, you
know, it's the culture. Um, fans are
great and I'm I'm excited to feel that
culture and it's it's a family culture
and I'm excited to be a part of it.
>> The fan base here is definitely very
passionate. What is your message to the
fans about what do they need to know
about you as a player?
>> Just get ready to see some high and far
kicks.
>> Far kicks. So, you averaged a
career-high 49 yards per punt last year
and you were very precise. What are your
goals for this season? Um, I I feel like
in the my time in the league, I've
gotten better each year, and I'm looking
forward to just keep getting better and
keep improving my game as the best I
can.
>> You mentioned that there are a couple of
players you're looking forward to
playing with. Who are they?
>> Uh, Zack Wood and Charlie Smith. Um, I
go way back with with Zack. Uh, him,
Thomas, and Will used to come to Two
Lane to uh work out there when they
couldn't use this facility in the
offseason. And um so I've been catching
snaps from him, playing catch with him
since my freshman year at Two Lane. Um I
just met Charlie a couple hours ago and
he's a great guy. A little hard to
understand, but we'll we'll we'll get
there. Um but I actually am excited to
play with Rajan, right? I played against
him in high school uh two times. So uh
know him and his family pretty well.
>> And in high school, you weren't a
punter.
>> Nope.
>> So he's a defensive player and you were
a quarterback.
>> Yeah. So that that's definitely
different dynamic.
>> Oh yeah, I I threw a touchdown or two on
him.
>> Okay, good. I like that. [laughter]
You're gonna have to remember to bring
that back up to him.
>> When you're thinking about being able to
walk into the locker room and the
culture that the Saints bring and being
a part of this organization,
>> what do you hope that you bring to this
place?
>> I just hope that I can help continue the
culture that uh Coach Moore brought in
last year. And um I I hope that I can
lead by example. I tend to be a little
bit more softspoken, but um I like to
like let my play uh do the talking.
>> This year they're building off of last
year's momentum. What are your
expectations for a successful season for
you?
>> Um just go about it one one punt at a
time, one game at a time, and keep
stacking days. And um if we all do that
as a team, we're going to like the
result at the end.
>> All right. Off the field, you got some
stuff going on
>> cuz you are expecting a little boy.
>> I am. Yes.
>> Are you excited?
>> Very excited. It's coming way too quick,
but we're excited.
>> All right. We're looking forward to it,
and we can't wait to have you here on
the field with the Saints.
>> Thank you.